William S. Rosecrans Papers
William S. Rosecrans Papers,
- Framed etching of General Rosecrans, Added January, 1982.
Totten, Joseph G. (Letters from) Box 2, folder 126, 167
Box 3, folders 34, 120, 129
Box 4, folders 17, 25
Totten, Joseph G. (Letters to) Box 44, folders 7, 10, 12, 17
Box 46, folder 11
Totten, Joseph G. (Mention of) Box 2, folders 82, 128, 157
Box 3, folder 67
Box 4, folder 15
Box 43, folder 133
Box 59, folders 2, 30
Box 80, folder 1
Tower, Zealous B. (Letter from) Box 2, folder 136
Townsend, Edward D. (Letters from) Box 9, folders 9, 81, 88, 93, 101, 109, 114, 118, 126, 140, 147, 151, 153-154
Box 10, folders 1, 29, 46-47, 49-50, 64, 66, 75-77, 102-103, 109
Box 21, folder 89
Box 36, folders 56, 73
Box 37, folder 28
Box 40, folder 70
Townsend, Edward D. (Letters to) Box 46, folders 12, 85-87, 99, 136
Box 47, folder 41
Box 49, folders 2 (2 letters), 5
Box 50, folder 3
Trowbridge, William P. (Mention of) Box 2, folder 4
Truman, Benjamin C. (Letter from) Box 40, folder 117
Truman, Benjamin C. (Mention of) Box 9, folder 1
Turchin, John B. (Ivan V. Turchininoff) (Letter from) Box 8, folder 65
Tweed, William M. (Letter to) Box 50, folder 1
Tyler, John (Document signed by) Box 124, folder 2
Tyler, John (Mention of) Box 55, folder 32
Box 58, folders 41, 45
Union Contract Company of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia Box 21, folders 116-117
Box 24, folder 71
Box 25, folders 33, 67
Box 26, folder 39
Box 27, folder 161
Box 31, folder 44
Box 47, folders 92-139
Box 48, folders 1-15, passim
Box 90
Union Contract Company of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia See also: Interoceanic Railroad Concession (Mexico)
Union of Radicals, Milwaukee (Questionnaire on platform of, answered by Rosecrans) Box 39, folder 124
Union Pacific Railroad Company Box 11, folders 52, 54, 58, 68-69, 72, 108, 129
Box 12, folders 5, 106-108, 110
Box 15, folder 25
Box 21, folder 51
Box 22, folder 53
Box 26, folder 67
Box 68, folder 32
U.S. Army (Reform of, 1843-1857) Boxes 1-2
Box 58, passim
U.S. Military Academy, West Point, New York Boxes 1-2, passim
Box 6, folder 130
Box 9, folder 59
Box 10, folder 106
Box 14, folder 132
Box 15, folders 116, 137
Box 34, folder 123
Box 80, folder 1
Box 82, folder 4
U.S. Military Asylum, Washington, D.C. Box 2, folders 61-62, 78, 88, 130, 159
U.S. Patent Office Box 2, folder 103
Box 4, folders 19, 122
U.S. Sanitary Commission Box 8, folders 15, 37, 40, 142
Box 9, folder 65
The Ursulines (Convent at St. Martin's, Brown Company, Ohio) Boxes 63-64, 72-75
The Ursulines (Convent at Santa Rosa, California) Box 73, folders 46-50
Usher, John Palmer (Mention of) Box 19, folder 32
Valentine, John J. (Letter from) Box 40, folder 116
Vallandigham, Clement L. (Letter from) Box 80, folder 34
Vallandigham, Clement L. (Letters to) Box 80, folder 34 (7 letters)
Vallandigham, Clement L. (Mention of) Box 10, folders 13, 17
Box 42, folder 133
Vallarta, Ignacio L. (Letters from) Box 22, folders 96, 104, 118
Box 24, folder 90
Box 26, folders 36, 111
Vallejo, Mariano G. (Mention of) Box 12, folder 67
Van Buren, John D. (Letter from) Box 12, folder 6
Van Buren, Martin (Mention of) Box 1, folder 2
Van Cleve, Horatio P. (Letter from) Box 8, folder 75
Van Cleve, Horatio P.(Letter to) Box 46, folder 26
Van Derveer, Ferdinand (Letter from) Box 21, folder 56
Van Dorn, Earl (Mention of) Box 7, folders 86-87
Box 59, folder 59
Vera Cruz Railroad Boxes 15-16, passim
Box 22, folder 73
Box 61, folder 84
Veterans' Home Association, San Francisco Box 82, folders 7-8
Villard, Henry (Letter to) Box 52, folder 3
Villard, Henry (Mention of) Box 9, folders 36-37
Vincent, Thomas M. (Letters from) Box 53, folders 97, 99, 101
Vinton, John R. (Mention of) Box 58, folders 62, 74-79
Wade, Benjamin F. (Letters from) Box 2, folders 85, 109
Box 8, folder 31
Box 9, folder 50
Box 10, folders 169-170, 172
Box 11, folder 14
Wade, Benjamin F. (Letters to) Box 49, folder 2 (4 letters)
Wade, Benjamin F. (Mention of) Box 2, folder 110
Box 7, folder 150
Box 10, folder 139
Walker, Robert J. (Letter from) Box 14, folder 78
Walker, Robert J. (Letter to) Box 47, folder 45
Wallace, Lewis (Mention of) Box 8, folder 21
Box 59, folder 43
War of 1812: Box 78, folders 89, 92, 94, 98
Ward, Durbin (Letters from) Box 14, folders 95, 122
Washburne, Elihu B. (Letter from) Box 7, folder 148
Washington Naval Yard, Washington, D.C.: Box 3, folders 28-29, 82, 122
Washington, D.C., Star (Opposition to Rosecrans) Box 9, folder 41
Waters, Russell J. (Letter from) Box 54, folder 84
Watervliet Arsenal, West Troy, New York Box 1, folders 37, 46, 65,68, 70
Webster, Daniel (Mention of) Box 78, folders 88-89
Weed, Thurlow (Letter from) Box 33, folder 136
Weed, Thurlow (Letter to) Box 52, folder 1
Weller, John B. (Letter to) Box 49, folder 5
West Virginia (Coal mining in) Boxes 5-7
Western Coal Oil Company Box 9, folder 71
Box 20, folder 129
Western Railroad Company Box 4, folder 98A
Whelan, Richard V. (Letter from) Box 6, folder 18
Whig Party Box 67, folder 6
Whipple, William D. (Letter from) Box 15, folder 111
White, Andrew D.(Letter to) Box 52, folder 1
“White Sulphur Springs Letter” Box 12, folders 32, 50, 54-55, 58, 61-62
Box 47, folders 49-50
Willamette Valley, Oregon (Settlement of) Box 17, folder 80
Williams, Alpheus S. (Letters from) Box 18, folder 102
Box 21, folders 55, 60
Williams, Alpheus S. (Letter to) Box 50, folder 3
Williams, Robert (1829-1901) (Letters from) Box 9, folder 77,94
Box 10, folders 11, 30-31,65, 70, 115, 168
Williamson, Robert S. (Letters from) Box 1, folders 53-54, 102, 104-105
Box 2, folders 4, 11, 16, 20, 22
Williamson, Robert S. (Mention of) Box 2, folders 7, 36
Williston, Edward B. (Letters from) Box 20, folders 64, 76
Wilmington & Weldon Railroad Company Box 4, folder 94A
Winchester, Battle of, 1863 Box 9, folder 8
Winder, William II (Mention of) Box 78, folder 89
Women's Loyal National League (Their efforts to secure emancipation) Box 8, folder 163
Wood, Fernando (Letter from) Box 33, folder 140
Wood, Fernando (Letter to) Box 52, folder 1
Wood, Thomas J. (Letters from) Box 7, folder 141
Box 8, folders 76, 82
Box 25, folder 12
Wood, Thomas J. (Mention of) Box 9, folders 57, 62, 106, 109
Box 59, folder 42
Box 80, folder 35
Woodbury, Daniel P. (Letters from) Box 2, folders 82, 164
Woodbury, Daniel P. (Mention of) Box 59, folder 3
Woodman, Clarence E. (Letters from) Box 30, folder 88
Box 42, folder 19
Box 70, folder 84
Woodruff, Israel C. (Mention of) Box 2, folder 164
Woods, Leonard (Letters from) Box 2, folders 47, 58
Woods, Leonard (Letter to) Box 52, folder 1
Wool, John E. (Mention of) Box 3, folder 146
Box 5, folder 134A
Workingmen's Party Box 48, folder 58A
Wright, Hendrick B. (Letter to) Box 48, folder 34
Wright, Horatio G. (Letters from) Box 1, folders 71, 75
Box 7, folder 65
Box 40, folders 66, 69
Wright, Horatio G. (Letter to) Box 45, folder 31
Wright, Horatio G. (Mention of) Box 2, folder 154
Box 59, folder 3
Wright, Marcus J. (Letter from) Box 43, folder 41
Yadkin Navigation Company Box 6, folder 49
Yates, Richard (Letters from) Box 7, folder 63
Box 8, folder 42
Box 9, folder 89
Box 10, folders 17, 35
Yates, Richard (Letter to) Box 45, folder 68
Yates, Richard (Mention of) Box 59, folder 109
Yazoo Land Bill, 1814 Box 78, folder 96
Yazoo River Campaign, 1864 Box 8, folder 23
Young, Brigham - Mention of: Box 21, folder 63
Young, John R. (Letter from) Box 12, folder 41
Items Removed from Collection
Diplomatic Instructions of the Department of State, Mexico. Returned to A. Hunt.
Dispatches from United States Ministers to Mexico, August 12, 1868-July 5, 1869 (Roll 36). Returned to A. Hunt.
Dispatches from United States Ministers to Mexico, 1872-1874 (Rolls 46-50). Cataloged in Main Library's Microfilm Collection: Consult Main Library Catalog.
Original oil portrait of Ann Eliza (Hegeman) Rosecrans, by George P.A. Healy, 1862. In the Original Works of Art on Paper Collection (Collection 99, Map Room). Available at Department of Special Collections, UCLA.